(Raj:)Can I make you breakfast?
(Raj:)Admiral Ackbar's Snack Bar
is open for business.
(Penny:)No, thanks. Leonard and I
are just going to the funeral.
You sure? Not even coffee?
(Howard:)We have R2-Decaf.
(Howard:)Maybe a nice Cafe Au Leia?
(Raj:)And if you're not
in the mood for coffee,
(Raj:)I can always make you
a Chai Tea-3PO.
(Penny:)I get it-- like C-3PO.
(Penny:)What happened to me?
-Hey, Sheldon, you want anything?
-No, thank you.
(Howard:)You're being so quiet.
(Howard:)Are you upset
or are you just rebooting?
(Sheldon:)I'm fine.
(Penny:)Sweetie, are you sure you don't want
to come with us to the funeral?
(Sheldon:)I appreciate the offer,
but Arthur is gone
(Sheldon:)and there's nothing
I can do about it.
(Sheldon:)When Darth Vader
struck down Obi-Wan,
(Sheldon:)did Luke cry like a baby
and go to his funeral?
(Penny:)No, he blew up the Death Star.
Why do I know this?!
(Sheldon:)Arthur Jeffries was a scientist.